I can't forget everything, I can't forget all the dreams I've made
Of course, I'll always be with you
I'll be with you, I'll be with you
If I don't say something, I'll be with you
I'll be happy, I'll be with you
I'll be smiling with you
The time when the light shines
The smile of the light shines
You and you and you
If you love each other
It will become a reality
Is it really a reality?
When we began our history
We became a huge world
We know where this place is
We also know where this place is
We know where it is
Even if it is nothing
even if it is not a world
Even if it is not a world
It was fun to have fun together with Muka Muka!
Shimeida Muka Muka!
Hey, Yousou, you're always thinking about it!
If you're thinking about it, you'll be able to see it, right?
Here, Kinto!
Naaaah!
It's an epic game!
Look at this!
Yousou's not going to be able to see it!
Hey, stop!
Youga's here!
Um...
I heard something about Motto's world right now!
That's right!
Youga always said something about it!
Well, that's right!
Huh?
I wonder where we are now?
Is there an order?
That's right!
Since it's a game,
Youga has a lot of order!
It's called Takuma City, and it's called Musinkei!
It's called the world of Motto!
It's not like that!
I'm different!
I'm doing my best!
Hey!
Huh?
I'm still going far!
Ukanuka?
It's not good for you, Youga.
You're getting to know where you can go back to Motto's world.
Why?
I'm thinking about finding out where you can go back to.
What about the machine room?
There's nothing bad about it, but you're really moving more than I thought.
I don't know what to do, but I'm sure there's a way to deal with it.
Hurry up and study!
No, I don't think I can do it today.
I can't do it when I don't have to.
I'll be back in the middle of the day.
Huh?
I wonder if I'll be able to return to the world when I grow up?
I don't think so.
Ah!
I'm sure I'll be able to return to the world when I grow up.
I see.
I'm sure I'll be able to return to my own world.
What are you two doing?
We're looking for a good life for Shimei.
Shimei?
Are you sure you know Shimei is a difficult thing?
That's what Shigo is doing!
Huh?
I know that!
I was in the village when I went to the river.
Huh?
Ah!
I was in the village when I lived in the village.
That village was in the village!
Huh?
Does she really not know you?
Shimei has begun to compete with Shimi.
Can you change the world when Shimei carries it?
Yeah.
I was in the forest, too.
I was trying to give up the answer...
I was trying to give up the answer.
When I heard that Shimii will come back to me for a long time,
Huh?
That's why I've been looking for something that I've been looking for.
Is that so?
I like it. We're looking for it too.
Ah, Tokagiyo-san, don't take it too long.
Huh?
I'm looking for something that I've been looking for the most.
Let's go! Let's get started!
Ranko-chan!
Hey, Hetsu. I'm looking for something.
But what should I do?
Hey!
Hmm, I'm not sure if I'm going to get the rest of the island.
I wonder if that's what I'm going to do.
Ranko-san, what's the relationship between you two?
I thought you were going to make a deal.
I thought you were going to make a deal with me before I came to the island.
So I'm going to make a deal with you two.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, are you going to look for something that I'm not taking?
What do you have?
Really, my parents aren't taking right away.
Of course.
Is this the land?
Yes.
In the past, I was making a deal for you two.
The land I told you was a land that I was going to make for me.
I was making a deal for you two.
Yep, so what kind of land is that?
I don't really know about that.
Kaia Makuro!
I don't want to see a snake like that!
Let's go to the other side.
I'll take you out of here!
I'll do my best!
Hehehe!
Ah! Ah!
Is there something in there?
What's going on?
As expected, I'm not going to make a mistake.
I'm not going to make a mistake!
My face is just like you!
There are many different characters today.
I've heard that many of them are falling.
I wonder if anyone is trying to get in the way of falling.
Slow down, please.
Stab the wall and then get in the way.
This is it!
I'm looking forward to what kind of love it is!
Yeah!
It's going to be a good one!
Oh, no!
Huh? That's right. I thought it was a little smaller, but I'm looking for a place to live.
That's what I'm talking about, Koji.
The people around me are good people, Koji.
If you're going to live in a place like this, you're going to live, Koji.
Oh, it's a natural place to live in the environment.
That's right, Koji. I always say thank you, Koji.
I'll be back in a few more days.
I'll be back in a few days.
Wow, I'm so happy.
Huh?
Koji is a heavy dog.
That's what I'm talking about.
I did it, Koji.
Who gave this to me?
Oh, the Zassobudo?
What is it? It's not what I wanted to hear, but...
It's a big success, but I thought the Zassobudo would be great if I could make a video about it.
But I didn't succeed even before the rest of the world.
There was a place to live in this place.
Wow, a big dog.
It's amazing.
Wow, it looks like a big dog.
I'm going to stop it.
I'm going to stop it again.
I'm not going to stop it again.
That's right.
The Zassobudo is a big dog.
A big dog.
It's not what I want to know.
It's a big success.
I'll make a Zassobudo with the Zassobudo.
Hey, hey, don't look at me like this.
You know that, right?
Yeah, it's still there.
If it's like this, let's go to that room again.
Oh, no!
It's not like this.
It's not like that.
Wait, wait, wait!
I'm scared!
What?
You're just being scared!
You're scared!
It's a problem of the water.
I'm scared!
Hey, look at me, I'm scared!
Huh?
Oh, I'm scared!
I'm scared!
Thank you, I'm scared!
I don't even know you.
I'm scared, bye bye!
I can only think about everything that has a long history.
It's like I'm not going to stop here.
I want you to stop here and break into a tree tree Not even a tree tree's first time have a argument being this dirty.
It's like you want me to come here, right?
It's like you want me to come here.
Hey, I want you to come here.
Can you either give me a letaisia19 driver or leave it to me, perhaps?
Aren't you trying to survive behind him?
It's not like that face of my hand.
BUu Reishi Remui
Hey, hold it!!
Put it back!!
This應該 is a good tech weather
Many times it will feel much softer
Thanks manylaw
Please get rid of the powerful 1,000 spell
to eliminate this damage
What should I do ?
Goooood
It's getting bigger!
No, no!
Look at this!
I got a small piece of paper with a small piece of paper!
You're right!
Look at this!
I'm getting smaller!
I see!
If it's getting smaller, it'll be easier to get smaller.
You're right!
Uh-huh!
I'm getting smaller!
Oh, I see!
I see!
The mini skirt is too tight!
It's a little bit too long!
This paper is way too long for me!
I'm getting smaller!
I see!
I don't know anything!
Oh my God!
I see!
My eyes are tickling.
My eyes?
If you tell me, I can share the pain on my face.
Who is that?
Fine.
How Nai's jaw is so small?
Look at my face.
I can feel the pain on my face.
No way!
My eye is not向al.
It's okay.
But what can I do?
Oh, I see.
Don't do that! Look at the future!
You're such a fool!
That's a poison!
If you want to see your own face, you can see the darkness.
I don't want to do that.
Shrija!
Don't do that!
I'm scared!
What do you like?
I'm not going to cry.
I'm not going to cry!
Oh, I see.
I don't know if you'll be so worried, Mr. Kamenji.
Then...
I...
I can't!
Oh, it's just like this!
I can't do that!
What are you doing?
I'm not going to cry.
I was going to help you change earlier.
I'm not going to cry anymore!
Ah!
This is hard!
Help me!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Now, please don't do that again.
Oh...
I'm sure you're going to cry because you're not going to cry.
Huh?
Then, why are you so cold?
Because it's the same world as the cold.
I'm going to cry because I'm going to cry because I'm not going to cry.
If you want to change earlier, you have to go to the other side of the future.
You don't have to do that, right?
I'm going to do it.
Huh?
Hey!
I'm going to cry.
It's so cold.
I'm going to cry because I'm going to cry.
It's so beautiful.
I'm going to cry.
Hey, it's still hot.
Um, is that the scent of that scent?
No, it's here.
Oh, it's here.
If I go to the other side of the future, I'll go to the other side of the future.
Did you lose it?
I lost it a few years ago, but it's been 300 years.
Huh?
I'm sure of it, right?
Oh, that's right, that's right.
Is that true?
It looks like it's going to be a good game.
I don't even know where it's going to be.
I'm sure it's going to be a good game.
Huh?
Hey, there's something wrong here.
Is that true?
Oh, no.
Don't get cold.
Is it the world of the Koryu?
Is it really okay here, Father?
There's no way. It's a Kagami.
Is that water?
That's the same.
The Koryu island of the Koryu island.
It's the dream of the future of the future of the Kagami.
Well, since it's here, who knows where Kamedo's words are.
Is that the dream?
It's okay.
I'll see you guys later.
I'll show you the Kagami island.
Let's go, Tepa.
Everyone's watching.
Let's go.
Hey.
Ah!
I can't lose this time.
1,000!
Whoa!
What's this?
There's something!
This is it!
Whoa!
Kagami!
The future!
That's the same.
The Kagami is over?
The future of the Kagami is over, too.
Oh, my.
If you're able to come over here, you'll be able to come over here.
Please calm down, Lanka.
I'll be right back.
Ah, you're so annoying.
You don't know how to do it.
The future of the Kagami is over?
You're going back to the original.
Really?
Of course, Lanka.
If the future of the Kagami is over, you'll be able to see the future.
I see.
That's good.
Are you going to be the Kagami today?
You're going to be able to come over today?
Ah, I see.
The future of the Kagami is over, too.
That's right.
The water is going to go away.
One more time!
Tomorrow!
Oh!
The future of the Kagami is over, too.
Yeah!
That's right!
Anyway, if you see the future of the Kagami, you'll see the future of the Kagami.
That's good, Kagami.
That's right.
The future of the Kagami is over, too.
Ah, I see.
Kame!
The future of the Kagami is over, too.
That's good for both of us.
We can live in the future, too.
We can't lose this one.
Ah!
It's so cold.
What do you mean?
We didn't know the future of the Kagami is over.
That's not surprising.
It's such a good place here.
The weather is beautiful, and the air is delicious.
But, what was that?
I didn't see the cold in front of me.
Huh?
It's cold.
I see.
I had a lot of things today, so I'm tired.
So, it's a shame that I'm not looking for people to look for people.
It's a shame that the future of the Kagami is over,
and the future of the Kagami is over.
Is it a shame?
Yes.
If the Kagami is over, I'll go back to the Takagaya Shoten Island in the world of people.
Father...
Let's do our best here.
Yes.
飛び吐いてよ
朝を読み
塗り塗りの
イアンディスもいるの
時を越え
ここへきているへん
へん
夏
私たち
There will be no problem
If you're telepathy, your start is my mission
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Everyone's good, don't be so loud
I'm going to the sky
Look at me! I'm looking at Shinshey and Shasha's eyes
YUM!
I'm going to get a bag of food
Huh?
Where did I get this bag?
That's right, Muka Muka is born in Tamagoto, so I'm surprised!
So, Muka Muka is born in Tamagoto!
Next time on Muka Muka Paradais, Tamagode Muka Muka, please look forward to it!